I didn't wait till I got home see number
hundred like that's something good
enough one for me number 100 and then I
realized that's working apples that's
the whole point of doing these hundred
is that they're just gonna keep coming
and I can do as many of these as I want
but the point was to do 100 and then put
them out there for people to actually
hear about them and hopefully contact me
and get involved I'll do another video
hopefully the next one but maybe not
might have twenty ideas you know and
then for how to get in contact and how I
would like people to get involved I'd
just come here so that that's a little
scary
three hundred that bowl was a map which
can be added to the city map of course
of places of like frequent car accidents
and why they occurred and help the city
better with city planning you've been a
way for citizens to be in contact with
their government but that's made by the
citizens not the government because I
mean I don't engage with the City of
Vancouver on their own website really
figuring out what it like we had we
didn't listen to garbage strike it was
it snowed and Vancouver doesn't do well
in snow and the garbage wasn't able to
be collected and to be able to
communicate that better to people water
shortages in a way that's a two-way
conversation of like hey well we're
gonna do this street we're gonna sweet
like coordination between neighbors and
it's become much bigger kind of just
other ones included but just thinking
about making streets safer places where
there could be crosswalks places where
there needs to be blinking crosswalks
there's really bad it's talking brutal I
don't see them to like after so that is
Apple hundred it's not the best one
that's the whole point it doesn't need
to be perfect and I'm not going to be
hoarding my apples anymore so now I've
just got to figure out how to get these
hundred apples online and out to the
greater world